sadikhov.com 2015-03-26

# IT Certification Forum on Sadikhov.com, Certification Exams, MCITP, MCTS, CCNA, CCNP, CCIE

Sadikhov.com considers the privacy of its Users to be a serious issue. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

Sadikhov.com is a web site based in the United States. Our Web Site is located at [http://www.sadikhov.com](http://www.sadikhov.com/). Our principal activity is to allow IT professionals all over the world share their knowledge between each other and help in any technical problems.

Our privacy policy covers Sadikhov.com and its Web site:  
**Sadikhov.com**  
  
WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS   
This policy covers how Sadikhov.com treats personal information that Sadikhov.com collects and receives, including information related to Your past use of Sadikhov.com's Web Site products and services. Personal information is information about You that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Sadikhov.com does not own or control or to people that Sadikhov.com does not employ or manage.  
  
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE   
Sadikhov.com collects personal information whenever a User registers with Sadikhov.com forum, when you use Sadikhov.com's products or services, when you visit Sadikhov.com pages or the pages. Sadikhov.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register on the forum we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip/postal code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Sadikhov.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Sadikhov.com collects information about your transactions with us, including information about your use of any products and services that we offer. Sadikhov.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, operating system, and the page you request. Sadikhov.com uses information for the following general purposes: improve our services, contact you, conduct research and development, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients, customer administration and technical Web Site administration purposes. 

When a child under age 13 attempts to register with Sadikhov.com forum, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian create a Sadikhov.com Family Account to obtain parental permission. Sadikhov.com will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent’s permission. Sadikhov.com does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion.  
These reasonable efforts are intended to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection of the child's personal data for our internal use and disclosure to third parties.  
  
INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE   
Sadikhov.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
• We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
• We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Sadikhov.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
• We transfer information about you if Sadikhov.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Sadikhov.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Sadikhov.com will use reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal data is not disclosed to State/provincial, national, regional institutions and authorities, unless required by law or other regulation.  
Sadikhov.com displays targeted advertisements based on the site content, not on the personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria – for example, men ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.  
• Sadikhov.com does not provide any personal information to the Advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.  
• Sadikhov.com advertisers may include a wide range of companies, including financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).   
PURPOSE FOR COLLECTION  
We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than those purposes indicated when you provide informed consent at the time of collection. If we wish to use or disclose your personal data for new purposes, we will offer you the means to consent to those new purposes via a web-based interface, email, postal mail or telephone  
COOKIES  
Sadikhov.com may set and access Sadikhov.com cookies on your computer. Sadikhov.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Sadikhov.com’s cookies. Sadikhov.com uses web beacons to access Sadikhov.com cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Sadikhov.com products and services.  
YOUR ABILITY TO ACCESS, EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES   
  
**General**  
You can edit your Sadikhov.com Account Information, at any time. New categories of preferences may be added to the Account Preferences at any time.   
Certain communications from Sadikhov.com, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Sadikhov.com Newsletter, are considered part of Sadikhov.com membership and you may not opt out of receiving them. You can delete your Sadikhov.com Account by requesting account deletion from web administrator using contact form at http://www.sadikhov.com/contacts.php

**Access**   
Upon a request accompanied by reasonable proof of your identity, Sadikhov.com will, without any charge, provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate. Although we reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, we will give reasons for any such refusal. We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.  
You may also access your data in the “Personal Profile” area of the My Controls interface accessible at <http://www.sadikhov.com/forum>. You may contact us using the information listed in Section 10 of this Agreement (.Privacy Support and Contact Information.) to request access to, changes to or deletion of your personal information.  
  
CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY  
We limit employee access to your personal information to those employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We also employ physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information. Your Sadikhov.com Account Information and Profile are password-protected  
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
Sadikhov.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Sadikhov.com Account or by placing a prominent notice on our Web Site  
PRIVACY SUPPORT AND CONTACT INFORMATION  
If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form online at <http://www.sadikhov.com/contacts.php> or contact us by e-mail: admin@sadikhov.com
